notice for next time
3. please tell ieail doll that you have a CHOICE if you run and change it!
Yes, I heard that a new member joined JuiceJuice the other day.
Today is the day of Budokan, though.
The fact that we are gathered here means
It's the day to meet the new member!
Careers!
How do you like it? I'm so happy,
How do you feel? How are you guys feeling?
I had a presentation when I was there,
Do you ever change your mind?
Yes!
I joined Juice-Juice because of the audition,
I was also auditioning with Yuki-chan,
I was able to work with the same group for the first time in two years,
I was really looking forward to it.
When we were announcing the new members, I talked with the members of Juice-Juice about the fact that there was a new member in the sky,
Sakira Ishiyama contacted me and told me that she would support me,
Mifu and I were in the same group when we were trainees,
I was a trainee with Mifu and we were working at the same time.
I think it was a team competition,
At that time, she told me that she and Mifu had a lot of bullying scenes in the same single.
That was amazing!
It's amazing that we can perform in the same group.
It's amazing.
Are you excited too? Bullying.
I'm thrilled.
I'm both excited and thrilled,
I can't wait for it to come out.
Wow!
Let's do it then! Mifchan!
Let's go!
So, maybe you'll show up in style, Scootin?
I'm sure he'll make a good appearance.
Wow!
Good morning.
Why am I coming?
I've got mandarin oranges!
Aren't you Solo Solo?
Now, please introduce yourself.
I'm Mamifu Kawashita, a 15-year-old first-year high school student from Kyoto.
I look forward to working with you.
Pleased to meet you.
Wow.
I'm going to be leaving now.
No way!
Mifchan, how do you feel after meeting the members again?
I think they are real when they are open to the public.
But..,
Wow!
It's real!
Do you have any questions for Mifchan?
I have a question I've decided to ask,
There are people who are divided,
Please answer honestly.
Are you a Jacaica person? Are you an octopus?
I'm a squid person.
We have delicious squid at our restaurant,
Let's go eat it together.
Thank you very much.
I'm fine with octopus, too,
I'm satisfied.
What is your favorite flavor of ice cream?
It's so cute.
Ice cream?
We're the same.
We seem to get along well.
Yes!
Who is it?
Candlelight sushi.
Let's go to Candlelight Sushi together.
Good luck.
Let's go to Cat together sometime.
We're going out again. Eva.
No way. Thank you very much.
No way.
You mean Eva's going to be in the movie?
I don't think so.
She's cute. It's so cute.
It's been a while since you saw Eva, right?
About 8 days.
It's Eva.
Yes.
China Ikuta?
China Ikuta.
How tall are you?
I feel like I'm shrinking,
Shorter?
Sixteen-one centimeters.
The octopus is the most amazing.
The heels feel amazing.
Is the octopus tighter?
Please don't.
I'm wesen shrinking right now, so I'm thinking maybe my shrinking height is shrinking,
But I really feel like you came out with a lot of dignity,
I can imagine Juice-Juice's performance with a lot of confidence,
I would like to continue to work with them,I would like to continue to work with them, though,
If not that one, I guess,
I'm sure.
It's the color of the members.
It's the members' color.
You don't know, do you? Not yet.
You don't know, do you?
Well, I'd like to make an announcement,
Could you please close your eyes?
Keep your eyes closed and put your hands in the air,
Give me your hand.
Reach out your hand.
You're nervous, aren't you?
I touched you too much.
I'm going to leave it.
I'm not going to open it yet.
Is it warm?
It's warm.
Now, open your eyes. Go ahead.
Me? Red?
Yes, that's right.
Really me,
I closed my eyes too,
It looked like a light bubble green.
So, I can't help it if I chose it.
It is pure red.
Pure red.
It's pure red.
I think it fits very well.
Are you happy?
Yes, I am.
The image of red has become very deep,
Is that so?
What was your own image of red?
When I was a trainee,
I like colors that are a little more deep blue than blue.
That's my color.
Royal blue and pure.
Pure?
Pure.
Royal red.
No good.
Put them together.
Certainly.
Like that.
Pretty.
Pure pure pure.
Do it together.
Wanting to do it is fun.
It's fun.
And the male power trainee trainee place.
It was good.
The power of men.
Men's power.
Let's keep up the good work.
So, Mina-chan,
I'm glad to hear that you've been working with us since this summer,
We will start full-fledged activities together from this summer,
I would like to work with you with emphasis and tolerance,
I hope you will continue to support us.
Why don't we say it's our 10th anniversary?
Well, let's have them say "Se-no". Here we go.
Here we go. Se-no!
It's our 10th anniversary!
Bye bye!
Yes, bye-bye! How was it?
Me? Yes, it was great.
I really did announce that Mifchan would be joining us about two weeks ago, or maybe a week, so it was pretty early. So it happened pretty quickly. Time passed very quickly.
That's why every day seems to fly by.
I wondered when I would be able to meet Mifchan. When will I meet you? I was wondering when I would be able to see Mifchan, but surprisingly, I was able to see her right away.
But my heart is still pounding. Maybe I don't know yet. What do you think?
I should probably tell you about the change in my feelings, but what made me happiest was that I've been looking forward to hearing about your favorite ice cream.
Oh.
That's right.
I was happy to hear that, so I wanted to say, "Let's go out for ice cream next time,
I was happy to hear that, so I thought I would like to say to them, "Let's go out for ice cream next time.
Well, Mifchan will be there, so please get along with her.
Yes, I will do my best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Wow!
Geron
Akari, Yuru, Rei, Hime, Miai, Ichiko, Risa, Kisaki, Sakura, Akari, Shuifun
Yes, Risa, welcome to JuiceJuice.
We are going to perform in Mongo Time, so let's have fun together.
We have prepared a lot for this event, so let's not leave the current JuiceJuice behind and enjoy it as much as possible.
We are JuiceJuice!
Oh-kun, I found a toy for you.
He seems to be nervous.
He became a senior. Ringo is.
You can call me Ringo.
I'm really nervous, but I'm looking forward to it.
Please do.
Well, hello!
Sam!Sam!
Aah!
More!
Yes!
Thank you.
Juice-Juice.
Juice-Juice
Good evening everyone gathered at the Nippon Airway Pavilion!
Good evening!
We are Juice-Juice!
Juice-Juice
As announced the other day, a new member will be joining Juice-Juice.
I would like to immediately call out the new members.
Mifu Kojima, here you go!
We will go shortly.
I am so happy for you all.
Super-Orion Line, everyone,
Enjoy yourselves.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you very much. Okay, then,
Please introduce yourself to everyone.
I am Miho Kawashima, a new member of Juice-Juice, from Kyoto, a first-year high school student, 15 years old.
I look forward to working with you.
You sound fast.
It's red, but what is your member color, Miho?
Cure-less.
Well, Mi-chan.
I'm a little sad to leave you, but I'll see you again.
Take care.
Go home with a smile on your face.
With a smile.
Bye bye.
That's all.
Ten laps successfully completed.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for today.
Yes, first of all, I met the members today,
I met the members and stood on stage at the Nippon Budokan for the first time,
I met Juice-Juice fans for the first time,
I met Juice-Juice fans for the first time, heard their calls live for the first time, and so on,
All of them are really good memories for me,
Today was the day I was able to experience so many things,
It was a day that I experienced so many things, and I want to cherish it in the future.
I was told that my member color is pure red,
I didn't say anything about it to the fans,
I didn't say anything to the fans, but they immediately turned their penlights to the color of pure red,
Juice-Juice fans are really warm,
I was a little anxious about whether they would accept me or not,
I was a little worried about whether they would accept me or not,
But I was really happy and felt happy.
I was watching Juice-Juice's performance from the audience seats today,
I was watching Juice-Juice's performance from the audience, and the monitors looked really cool,
And Juice-Juice's performance was really powerful,
I was so excited watching their performance that I could not help but get into the groove,
I always thought it was really cool,
I've been thinking how cool they are, and I've been trying my best to perform as soon as possible,
I will do my best to perform as soon as possible so that my fans can see Miho Kawashima as Juice-Juice.
I am Miho Kawashima, the newest member of Juice-Juice.
Today was the first time for me to make my debut at the Nippon Budokan,
It was really an important event for Juice-Juice as it was our 10th anniversary,
I was really nervous,
I was really nervous, but everyone accepted me warmly,
I was really relieved,
I am really going to do my best in my performances.
I would be very happy if you could support me from now on.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you very much.